<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.print-manager</id>
  <extends>org.kde.systemsettings</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.kded</extends>
  <name>Printer Configuration</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Configuració de la impressora</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Druckereinrichtung</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Διαμόρφωση εκτυπωτή</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Printer Configuration</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Configuración de la impresora</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Inprimagailu konfiguratzea</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Configuration de l'imprimante</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Configurazione della stampante</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Printerconfiguratie</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Skrivaroppsett</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Ustawienia drukarki</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Configuração da Impressora</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Nastavenie tlačiarne</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Skrivarinställning</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Налаштування принтера</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxPrinter Configurationxx</name>
  <summary>Set up and configure printers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Instal·la i configura les impressores</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Drucker einrichten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Ρύθμιση και διαμόρφωση εκτυπωτών</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Set up and configure printers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Instalación y configuración de impresoras</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Ezarri eta konfiguratu inprimagailuak</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Installer et configurer les imprimantes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Imposta e configura le stampanti</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Printers instellen en configureren</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Set opp skrivarar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Ustawienia drukarki</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Definição e configuração de impressoras</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Nastaviť a nakonfigurovať tlačiarne</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Ställ in och anpassa skrivare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Встановлення та налаштовування принтерів</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxSet up and configure printersxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>This KDE Config tool lets you set up and configure printers.  It detects new printers, finds the available drivers and allows you to configure their settings.  You can print test pages and set sharing properties.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Aquesta eina de configuració del KDE permet instal·lar i configurar impressores. Detecta les impressores noves, cerca els controlador disponibles i permet configurar els seus paràmetres. Es poden imprimir pàgines de prova i definir les propietats de compartició.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Mit diesem KDE-Einrichtungsprogramm können Sie Drucker einrichten. Es erkennt neue Drucker, findet die verfügbaren Treiber und ermöglicht es Ihnen, deren Treiber einzustellen. Sie können Testseiten drucken und Freigabeeigenschaften festlegen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Αυτό το εργαλείο διαμόρφωσης του KDE σας επιτρέπει να ρυθμίσετε και να διαμορφώσετε εκτυπωτές. Ανιχνεύει νέους εκτυπωτές, βρίσκει τους διαθέσιμους οδηγούς και σας επιτρέπει να διαμορφώσετε τις ρυθμίσεις τους. Μπορείτε να εκτυπώσετε δοκιμαστικές σελίδες και να ρυθμίσετε τις ιδιότητες κοινής χρήσης.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">This KDE Config tool lets you set up and configure printers. It detects new printers, finds the available drivers and allows you to configure their settings. You can print test pages and set sharing properties.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Esta herramienta de KDE le permite instalar y configurar impresoras. Detecta nuevas impresoras, encuentra los controladores disponibles y le permite configurar sus ajustes. Puede imprimir páginas de pruebas y definir las propiedades para compartir las impresoras.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">KDEren konfiguratzeko tresna honek inprimagailuak ezartzen eta konfiguratzen uzten dizu. Inprimagailu berriak hautematen ditu, gidari erabilgarriak aurkitzen ditu eta haien ezarpenak konfiguratzen uzten dizu. Proba-orriak inprimatu eta partekatzeko propietateak ezarri ditzakezu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Cet outil de configuration KDE vous permet d'installer et de configurer les imprimantes. Il détecte les nouvelles imprimantes, trouve les pilotes disponibles et vous permet de les configurer. Vous pouvez imprimer des pages de test et définir les propriétés de partage.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Questo strumento di configurazione di KDE permette di impostare e configurare le stampanti. Rileva le nuove stampanti, trova tutti i driver disponibili e ti permette di configurarne le relative impostazioni. Puoi stampare pagine di prova ed impostare le proprietà di condivisione.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Dit hulpmiddel voor configuratie van laat u printers instellen en configureren. Het detecteert nieuwe printers, vindt de beschikbare stuurprogramma's en biedt u aan om hun instellingen te configureren. U kunt testpagina's afdrukken en eigenschappen voor delen instellen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Dette verktøyet lèt deg setja opp skrivarar. Det kan oppdaga nye skrivarar, finna tilgjengelege drivarar og setja dei opp. Du kan skriva ut testutskrifter og endra delingsinnstillingar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Narzędzie ustawień KDE umożliwia ustawienie drukarek. Wykrywa nowe drukarki, znajduje dostępne sterowniki i umożliwia ich ustawienie. Można drukować strony próbne i nadawać ustawienia współdzielenia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Esta ferramenta de configuração do KDE permite-lhe definir e configurar impressoras. Detecta impressoras novas, descobre os controladores disponíveis e permite-lhe configurar as suas opções. Poderá imprimir páginas de testes e definir as propriedades de partilha.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Tento KDE nástroj vám umožní nastaviť a nakonfigurovať tlačiarne. Zistí nové tlačiarne, nájde dostupné ovládače a umožní vám nastaviť ich nastavenia. Môžete tlačiť testovacie stránky a nastaviť možnosti zdieľania.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Det här KDE-inställningsverktyget låter dig ställa in och anpassa skrivare. Det detekterar nya skrivare, hittar tillgängliga drivrutiner och låter dig anpassa deras inställningar. Du kan skriva ut testsidor och ställa in delningsegenskaper.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою цього засобу налаштовування KDE ви зможете встановити початкові параметри роботи принтерів та налаштувати принтери. Він здатний виявляти нові принтери, визначати доступні для них драйвери та налаштовувати параметри роботи цих драйверів. Ви можете друкувати тестові сторінки та визначати параметри спільного користування принтерами.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThis KDE Config tool lets you set up and configure printers. It detects new printers, finds the available drivers and allows you to configure their settings. You can print test pages and set sharing properties.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/buglist.cgi?component=general&amp;product=print-manager&amp;resolution=---</url>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Printer settings.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Paràmetres de la impressora.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Druckereinstellungen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Ρυθμίσεις εκτυπωτή.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Printer settings.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Preferencias de la impresora.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Inprimagailu ezarpenak.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Paramètres de l'imprimante.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Impostazioni della stampante.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Printerinstellingen.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Skrivarinnstillingar.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Ustawienia drukarki</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Configuração da impressora.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Nastavenia tlačiarne.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Skrivarinställningar.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Параметри принтерів.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxPrinter settings.xx</caption>
      <image type="source" width="1028" height="757">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/print-manager/print-manager.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>System</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">printer</icon>
</component>
